# Naina Sharma

nainasharmaofficial5@gmail.com / 8010225842 / New Delhi, Delhi

#### Summary

Experienced content writer passionate about captivating readers and driving conversions. Specializing in SEO and brand storytelling, I create engaging content that resonates with audiences. MBA-educated with a strategic mindset, I help businesses elevate their content marketing efforts. Let's connect and craft content that converts!

# **Experience**

# **Content Writer & Strategic Manager**

Lfyd Services Pvt. Ltd. • Bhubaneswar, Odisha

11/2021 - Present

- Manage and archive quality documentation and participate in internal and external quality meetings.
- · Contents For Website making.
- · Daily Blogs.
- · Daily Emails.
- · Supported management team with expert skills in writing.
- My article got published in BusinessWorld magazine

# **Content Writer Intern**

Quardiro Technology LLP • Gurugram, Haryana

07/2021 - 10/2021

My responsibility was to provide daily blogs and articles for the company's daily operations. Moreover, to create strategic technology content.

# **Content Writer Intern**

Ungrezi Pvt. Ltd. • Mansarovar, Jaipur 06/2021 - 07/2021

- For this internship, we would create a syllabus for students in various grades for multiple classes and disciplines.
- I was acknowledged and recognized also for my work.

# **Business Development Associate Intern**

WeSettle • Gurugram, Haryana

10/2020 - 11/2020

My task was to persuade college students to rent a PG and sell coupons to them.

# **Content Writer Intern**

Yuvastamb Foundation ullet Gurugram, Haryana

06/2020 - 09/2020

- My job during my content writing internship was to research the assigned topics, which were typically historical in nature, and then create original content. after which it will be published in "India's Youth Post."
- They have also created a short movie story with much of my content for their social media handles.

#### **Skills**

Communication skills, Microsoft word, SEO Tools, Blogging, Creative Writing, Writing Skills, Strategic Writing, Social Media Writing, Web Writing, Translation, Computer literacy, Time management, English, Leadership

#### **Education**

#### **MBA**

IGNOU • New Delhi, Delhi

07/2022

Skills: Data Analysis · Team Leadership · Project Management · Operations Research · Leadership

### Bachelor's of Science

Lady Irwin College, University of Delhi • New Delhi, Delhi 05/2022

- · Received Certificates.
- · Specialized in Food Technology.
- Volunteered in various programmes.
- Graduated From First division with distinction.

.

## **Medical Science**

Kendriya Vidyalaya No. 2 • New Delhi, Delhi 03/2019

- Activities and societies: Sports, NCC & Student's Council Activities and societies: Sports, NCC & Student's Council.
- I was enrolled as a Rank holder cadet in school level as a JW Cadet. I have been in KVS National Sports Meet 2016–17 from Delhi region in shooting. I was first best shooter in my school from KVS sports meet and in NCC also I was best firer from Delhi Directorate.
- Activities and societies: Attended National Camp THAL SAINIK CAMP (2016)
- Participated in DELHI BEST CADET COMPETITION (2016) and won 1st position.
- Received A Certificate, B Certificate & C Certificate, scholarship, and Two merit certificates. Received A Certificate, B Certificate & C Certificate, scholarship, and Two merit certificates.
- Received 2 Scholarships.

#### Languages

English, Hindi, Punjabi

#### Certificates

Creative Writing, Digital Marketing, Social Media Marketing, SEO Domination

#### **Awards**

1st best Shooter, National Shooter, 1st Best cadet Delhi Directorate, Scholarships, Delhi Wall Art Competition

# **Portfolio**

- 1. <a href="https://deliberationsofnaina.wordpress.com/">https://deliberationsofnaina.wordpress.com/</a> Link to my blogging website.
- 2. <a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1zwING3NLaHC4">https://docs.google.com/document/d/1zwING3NLaHC4</a> lticcPXZ-02VMQdltCTIkGY06GtQIM/edit? usp=share link Links to few of my Content work samples.